{ "cards":[
    {
        "front": "Method that retains fragments, called in the fragments onCreate method",
        "back": "setRetainedInstance(true)"
    },
    {
        "front": "Generic  steps to conntect to Http and download JSON",
        "back": "create URL()\ncreate HttpURLConnectioin()\ncreate ByteArrayOutputStream()\ncreate InputStream()\nget the HttpUrlConnection response if OK\nreadin the bytes"
    },
    {
        "front": "Permission must be asked to network by.",
        "back": "Adding newtworking permissoin to the manifest- AndroidManefest.xml\n<uses-permissions android:name=\"android.permission.INTERNET\" />"
    },
    {
        "front": "Networking should be run on the main UI thread or a backgrouind thread.",
        "back": "background thread, using for example AsyncTask."
    },
    {
        "front": "API",
        "back": "application programming interface"
    },
    {
        "front": "Popular format that data is sent in for web services",
        "back": "JSON"
    },
    {
        "front": "API are mostly in this format",
        "back": "REST"
    },
    {
        "front": "Helper class for building or manipulating URI references.",
        "back": "Uri.Builder"
    },
    {
        "front": "JSON objects used to parse JSON.",
        "back": "JSONObject and JSONArray"
    },
    {
        "front": "Class to do background Http work.",
        "back": "AsyncTack."
    }
]
}
